Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
- Loew's
  - Moulin Rouge, April 6, 1934 (Box 2)
    46th St. Theatre: Constance Bennett in "Moulin Rouge"; Robert Montgomery in "Mystery of Mr. X"; Warren William in "Bedside"; and more. Boro Park Theatre: John Barrymore in "Long Lost Father"; "Hips, Hips, Hooray"; "Midnight"; "Woman Unafraid"; and more.
- Loew's 7th Avenue
  - Kiki, March 23, 1925 (Box 2)
    "Kiki" a character study by Andre Picard. Staged by Luke Conness. Settings by J. D. Braddon. Associate Director, John Duggan. Organist, Lew Frey. With Anne Bronaugh, Carl Brickett, Harold Kennedy, William Jeffrey, Mark Kent, Anthony Stanford et al.
- Loew's Kings
  - A Lady To Love, March 22, 1930 (Box 2)
    First Spring Carnival Show featuring music selections, news, organ solo, stage presentation of "Color Rhythm" by Edgar Allen Woolf featuring Dave Schooler; and the Feature Presentation of "A Lady To Love" with Vilma Banky, Edward G. Robinson et al.
- Majestic Theatre
  - Flo Flo, November 28, 1904 (Box 2)
    E.D. Stair and George H. Nicolai present Stella Mayhew in a musical Comedy, in Two Acts, "Flo Flo." Book and lyrics by Collin Davis, Music by Howard Whitney, Staged by Harry T. MacConnell. Also with Matthew Kennedy, Charles A. Pusey et al.
  - Buster Brown, August 19, 1905 (Box 2)
    Melville B. Raymond's cartoon comedy, "Buster Brown." Richard F. Outcault - author, inventor, designer. With Master Gabriel, George Ali, Al. Lamar, Burt Jordan et al.
  - The German Gipsy, January 15, 1906 (Box 2)
    Sidney R. Ellis presents Al. H. Wilson in "The German Gipsy" by Robert Sidney. Also with Thos. M. Hunter, Rose O'Neal, Al T. Holstein, Chris Naumann et al. Stage Manager, Ross O'Neal.
  - Way Down East, March 5, 1906 (Box 2)
    Wm. Brady's production of "Way Down East" by Lottie Blair Parker. Elaborated by Joseph R. Grismer. With Phoebe Davies, Robert A. Fischer, Mary Davenport, Thurlow Bergen, Genevieve Cliff, Frank Currier et al.
  - The Princess Pat, February 21, 1916 (Box 2)
    John Cort presents "The Princess Pat." Book and lyrics by Henry Blossom. Music by Victor Herbert. Staged by Fred. G. Latham. With Leonora Novasio, Martin Hayden, Sam. B. Hardy, Robert Ober, Alexander Clark et al.
  - A Lady's Name, October 23, 1916 (Box 2)
    The Messrs. Shubert present Marie Tempest in "A Lady's Name" by Cyril Harcourt, author of "A Pair of Silk Stockings" and "A Place in the Sun." Also with Julia Chippendale, Maud Andrew, John Sharkey, Mayne Lynton et al.
  - The Silent Witness, October 30, 1916 (Box 2)
    H. H. Frazee presents "The Silent Witness" by Otto Hauerbach. With Helen Reimer, John Houston, Helen Holmes, David Higgins, Blossom Bird et al. Stage Manager, W. H. Gregory.
  - Very Good Eddie, November 13, 1916 (Box 2)
    The Marbury-Comstock Company Presents "Very Good Eddie." Book by Philip Bartholomae and Guy Bolton. Lyrics by Schuyler Greene. Music by Jerome Kern. With Benjamin F. Wright, James Lounsbery, Lew Fullerton, Earl Benham, Ada Lewis et al.
  - Katinka, November 27, 1916 (Box 2)
    Arthur Hammerstein Presents the Musical Play "Katinka." Book and lyrics by Otto Hauerbach. Music by Rudolph Friml. With Jane Castle, Daniel J. Sullivan, John Roberts, S. Paul Veron, Margaret Owen, Marquita Dwight et al.
  - Rich Man, Poor Man, December 4, 1916 (Box 2)
    George Broadhurst Presents his new play, "Rich Man, Poor Man." Based on the story by Maximilian Foster. With John Bowers, William B. Mack, Brandon Hurst, Frank Westerton, Rudolph Cameron, Emmett Shackelford et al.
  - His Majesty Bunker Bean, January 15, 1917 (Box 2)
    William H. Currie Presents Taylor Holmes in "His Majesty Bunker Bean" by Lee Wilson Dodd. From the novel by Harry Leon Wilson. Staged by Robert Milton. Also with Charles Abbe, Robert Toms, Horace Mitchell, Florence Shirley, Stanley Wood et al.
  - Getting Married, February 5, 1917 (Box 2)
    William Faversham Presenting and Appearing in "Getting Married" by George Bernard Shaw. Also with Henrietta Crosman, Mrs. Edmund Gurney, John Harwood, Lumsden Hare, Hilda Spong, George Fitzgerald et al.
  - The Lodger, March 5, 1917 (Box 2)
    Adapted by Horace Annesley Vachell from the novel by Mrs. Belle Lowndes,"The Lodger." With Beryl Mercer, Harry Ashford, Phyllis Relph, Thomas Robinson, Lionel Atwill, Frederick Annerley, Frank Howson et al.
  - Canary Cottage, May 28, 1917 (Box 2)
    Oliver Morosco Presents "Canary Cottage," a musical farce. Book by Oliver Morosco and Elmer Harris. Music and lyrics by Earl Carroll. With Arthur Burckley, James Dunn, Grace Ellsworth, Lillian Boardman, Charles Ruggles et al.
  - The Masquerader, January 21, 1918 (Box 2)
    Richard Walton Tully Presents, Guy Bates Post in, "The Masquerader." A play by John Hunter Booth, based upon the novel by Katherine Cecil Thurston. Also with Lionel Belmore, Gerry Cornell, Lurita Stone, Thais Lawton, Georgia Mai Fursman et al.
  - The Crimson Alibi, January 1, 1920 (Box 2)
  - His Honor, Abe Potash, April 26, 1920 (Box 2)
    A. H. Woods presents, Barney Bernard in, "His Honor, Abe Potash." A comedy by Montague Glass and Jules Eckert Goodman. Staged under the direction of Willard Mack. Also with Mathilde Cottrelly, Lucille English et al.
  - Parlor, Bedroom and Bath, May 3, 1920 (Box 2)
    A. H. Woods presents "Parlor, Bedroom and Bath" by C. W. Bell and Mark Swan. A tale of a wayside Inn. Staged by Bertram Harrison. With Agnes Jeppson, Gail Sheldon, Pearl Ford, Belle Mitchell et al.
  - The Passion Flower, May 31, 1920 (Box 2)
    Richard G. Herndon presents "The Passion Flower" by Jacinto Benavente. Translated by John Garrett Underhill, Staged by Alfred Hickman. With Nance O'Neil, Annette Westbay, Clara T. Bracey, Aldeah Wise, Mercedes De Cordoba, Lillian Aune et al.
  - Blossom Time, March 24, 1924 (Box 2)
    Messrs. Shubert present, The Franz Schubert Operetta, "Blossom Time." Score and Story: Franz Schubert. Adapted by A. M. Willner and H. Reichert. With Edith Thayer, Zoe Barnett, Marion Abel, Sonya Leyton, Howard Marsh et al.
  - Sally, March 23, 1925 (Box 2)
    Nicolai-Welch-DeMilt, Inc. bring you Ziegfeld's "Sally." Lyrics: Clifford Grey, Book: Guy Bolton, Music: Jerome Kern, Production: Edward Royce. With Ross Snow, Mary Connors, Adeline Cooley, William H. Power, Lee Johnstone et al.
  - The Letter, February 6, 1928 (Box 2)
    Messmore Kendall presents "The Letter" by W. Somerset Maugham. Staged by Guthrie McClintic. With Katharine Cornell, Swezo Kotoro, John Buckler, Allan Jeayes, J. W. Austin et al.
  - The Legacy, September 24, [1928] (Box 2)
    A.H. Woods & Gilbert Miller present Florence Reed in "The Legacy (La Ripose)" by Francois Noziere. Translated and adapted by Sidney Howard.
  - The Scarlet Woman, October 29, [1928] (Box 2)
    L. C. Wiswell, Inc., presents Pauline Frederick in, "The Scarlet Woman." By Zelda Sears and Reita Lambert. Staged by A. Leslie Pearce. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
  - Melo, April 6, 1931 (Box 2)
    Lee Shubert presents "Melo." Adapted by Arthur Pollock from the French of Henri Bernstein. With Basil Rathbone, Edna Best, Earle Larimore et al. Settings by Rollo Wayne, Staged by Marcel Varnel.
  - Pigeons and People, April 17, 1933 (Box 2)
    George M. Cohan and his Company of Players in "Pigeons and People." Directed by Sam Forrest. With Walter Gilbert, George M. Cohan, Arvid Paulson, Olive Reeves-Smith et al.
  - Dinner at Eight, May 22, 1933 (Box 2)
    Sam H. Harris presents "Dinner at Eight" by George S. Kaufman and Edna Ferber. Staged by George S. Kaufman, Settings by Livingston Plati. With Ann Andrews, Mary Murray, Gregory Gaye, Charles Trowbridge et al.
  - The Patsy, February 21, 1938 (Box 2)
    Helen Ford in "The Patsy" by Barry Connors. Staged by B. J. Steele. With Homer Miles, Editha Ketchum, Kathleen Kidder, Helen Ford, Cledge Roberts, Butler Hixon, Don Haggerty. Stage Manager: Louis Tanner.
- Manhattan Beach Theatre
  - The Last Days of Pompeii, 1889 (Box 2)
    "The Last Days of Pompeii." Colossal Painting and Pyrotechnic Effects. Arranged and Produced by James Pain & Sons.
  - Robin Hood, September 4, 1897 (Box 2)
    Sousa's Grand Concerts; The "Bostonians" in "Robin Hood" by Reginald DeKoven and Harry B. Smith. With Henry Clay Barnabee, William E. Philp, W. H. MacDonald et al; Pain's Pyro-Spectacle, "Greece and Turkey"; and more.
  - El Capitan, June 27, 1898 (Box 2)
    Grand Concerts by Victor Herbert's 22d Regt. Band; "El Capitan" by The De Wolf Hopper Opera Company with DeWolf Hopper, Alfred Klein, Thomas S. Guise et al; Pains Pyro-Spectacle "Fall of Manila"; and more.
  - The Serenade, August 26, 1898 (Box 2)
    Grand Concerts by Victor Herbert's 22d Regt. Band; The Famous Original Bostonians in "The Serenade." Music: Victor Herbert, Libretto: Harry B. Smith. With Henry Clay Barnabee et al; Pains Pyro-Spectacle "Fall of Manila"; and more.
  - The Idol's Eye, June 26, 1899 (Box 2)
    Sousa's Grand Concerts; "The Idol's Eye" by Harry B. Smith and Victor Herbert. With Frank Daniels, Alf C. Wheelan et al. Musical and Stage Director: L. F. Gottschalk; Frank Daniels in "The Wizard of the Nile"; Pain's Fireworks Enclosure; and more.
  - The Wizard of the Nile, July 6, 1899 (Box 2)
    Sousa's Grand Concerts; Kirk La Shelle presents Smith and Herbert's Greatest Comic Opera Success "The Wizard of the Nile." With Frank Daniels, Norma Kopp et al; Pain's Fireworks Enclosure; and more.
  - A Runaway Girl, June 23, 1900 (Box 2)
    The Austin Daly Musical Company, including James T. Powers, in "A Runaway Girl" by Seymour Hicks and Harry Nichols; Fanciulli's Grand Concert.
  - Great American Minstrels, July 16, 1900 (Box 2)
    Primrose & Dockstader's Great American Minstrels; Fanciulli's 71st Regiment Band; Pain's Fireworks Enclosure Grand Spectacle, "Fujiyama."
  - Miss Simplicity, June 30, 1902 (Box 2)
    Grand Concert by Shannon's 23d Regiment Band; Kirk La Shelle presents Frank Daniels and his Company in "Miss Simplicity," Book: R. A. Barnet, Music: H. L. Heartz; Pain's Spectacle, "The Burning of Rome."
  - The Show Girl, Or, The Cap of Fortune, July 14, 1902 (Box 2)
    Grand Concert by Shannon's 23d Regiment Band; Rice's (Edward E.) Production of "The Show Girl, Or, The Cap of Fortune" by R. A. Barnet. With Frank Lalor, Frank C. Young et al; Pain's Spectacle, "The Burning of Rome."
  - The Sultan of Sulu, June 29, 1903 (Box 2)
    Grand Concert by Shannon's 23d Regiment Band; Edward E. Rice's Sunday Pops; Henry W. Savage presents George Ade's Musical, "The Sultan of Sulu." Music by Alfred G. Wathall; The Spectacle, "Pompeii," in Pain's Fireworks Enclosure.
  - The Sultan of Sulu, July 6, 1903 (Box 2)
  - Lew Dockstader and His Minstrel Company, July 13, 1903 (Box 2)
    Grand Concert by Shannon's 23d Regiment Band; Lew Dockstader and His Minstrel Co.; The Spectacle, "Pompeii," in Pain's Fireworks Enclosure.
- Marcy
  - The Letter, January 16-22, [1941] (Box 2)
    Bette Davis in W. Somerset Maugham's "The Letter"; Abbott & Costello in "One Night in the Tropics"; New Chapter of "The Green Hornet Strikes Again"; Baby Sandy in "Sandy Gets Her Man"; Boris Karloff in "The Ape."
- Midway
  - Cowboy From Brooklyn, July 26-August 1, [1942] (Box 2)
    "Cowboy From Brooklyn" With Dick Powell, Priscilla Lane; "She's In The Army" with Lucille Gleason; "In This Our Life" with Bette Davis, Olivia De Havilland; "Mexican Spitfire At Sea" with Lupe Velez; "Moontide" with Jean Gabin, Ida Lupino; and more.
- Midwood Theatre
  - A Virgin Paradise, November 14, [1921] (Box 2)
    Midwood Concert Orchestra, Max Margolis, Conducting. "A Virgin Paradise" by Hiram Percy Maxim. With Pearl White, Robert Elliott et al. Also, Sessue Hayakawa in "Where Lights Are Low." Corinne Griffith in "The Single Track"; and more. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
- Minsky's Theatre
  - Goona-Goona, Or Bust [2 copies], March 6, 1933 (Box 2)
    "Goona-Goona, Or Bust" a Minsky burlesque in two acts and twenty-eight scenes. Dance episodes conceived and staged by Palmiere Brandeau, Dialogue by Buddy Abbott. With Mae Brown, Carolyn Snowden et al. Orchestra directed by Charles Schwartz.
- Momart
  - The Bride Wore Red, February 19, [1938] (Box 2)
    "The Bride Wore Red"with Joan Crawford; "Conquest" with Greta Garbo; "Night Club Scandal" with John Barrymore; "The Awful Truth" with Cary Grant; "Thoroughbreds Don't Cry" with Mickey Rooney; "Victoria The Great" with Anna Neagle; and more.
- Montauk Theatre
  - The Little Minister, December 12, 1898 (Box 2)
    Mr. Charles Frohman presents "The Little Minister" by J. M. Barrie. A Comedy in Four Acts. With Robert Edeson, Eugene Jepson, George Irving, Maude Adams, Margaret Gordon, Frederick Spencer et al. Stage Manager, Ira A. Hards.
  - Hurly Burly, April 27, 1899 (Box 2)
    Annual Entertainment, Brooklyn Lodge: B.P.O. Elks No. 22. "Hurly Burly" Book by Harry B. Smith and Edgar Smith. Music by John Stromberg. With Charles J. Ross et al. "Catherine" Dialogue by Edgar Smith, Lyrics by Harry B. Smith. With Chas. J. Ross et al.
  - The Belle of New York (Box 2)
  - On The Quiet, September 2, 1901 (Box 2)
    William Collier in the Comedy "On The Quiet" by Augustus Thomas. Directed by Jacob Litt. Also with, Helena Collier, Cranley Douglas, George W. Parsons, John Saville et al.
  - The Stroller's, September 9, 1901 (Box 2)
    Francis Wilson and Company in George W. Lederer's Musical Comedy, "The Strollers." Adapted from the German of L. Krenn and C. Lindau. Book by Harry B. Smith; Music by Ludwig Englander. Also with, Edwin Foy, D. L. Don et al.
  - Lovers' Lane, September 23, 1901 (Box 2)
    Wm. A. Brady presents "Lovers' Lane" by Clyde Fitch. With Ernest Hastings, Franklyn Roberts, Frank C. Hartwell, A. L. Traherne, Arthur C. Sanders, Julian Barton et al.
  - Captain Jinks of the Horse Marines, October 7, 1901 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents the Comedy, "Captain Jinks of the Horse Marines" by Clyde Fitch. With Ethel Barrrymore, George W. Howard, Francis Byrne, H. S. Tabor, George W. Barnum, John R. Sumner et al.
  - Rogers Brothers in Washington, October 21, 1901 (Box 2)
    The Klaw & Erlanger Comedy Co. and Gus and Max Rogers in, John J. McNally's vaudeville farce, "Rogers Brothers in Washington." Lyrics by Harry B. Smith; Music by Maurice Levi. With Gus Rogers, Max Rogers, William West et al.
  - The Climbers, October 28, [1901] (Box 2)
    Amelia Bingham Company in "The Climbers." A Drama by Clyde Fitch. Stage Manager, Alfred Fisher. With Robert Edeson, Frank Worthing, Ferdinand Gottschalk, James Carew, James Bennett Sturgis et al. Dated via coverage in Brooklyn Life.
  - King Charles I, November 11, 1901 (Box 2)
    Henry Irving, Ellen Terry and The London Lyceum Company in "King Charles I" by W. G. Wills. Also with, Mrs. F. Tyars, J. H. Barnes, A. Royston, W. Lugg et al.
  - Louis XI, November 11, 1901 (Box 2)
    Henry Irving, Ellen Terry and The London Lyceum Company in, Casimir Delavigne's Play, "Louis XI." Adapted and arranged by Dion Boucicault. Also with, Mabel Hackney, Laurence Irving, Mrs. F. Tyars, J. H. Barnes et al.
  - Mrs. Dane's Defense, November 25, 1901 (Box 2)
    Twelfth Annual Autumn Tour of Charles Frohman's Empire Theatre Company presenting "Mrs. Dane's Defense." A Play, in Four Acts, by Henry Arthur Jones. With Charles Richman, George Cooper, W. H. Crompton et al.
  - A Royal Rival, December 9, 1901 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents, William Faversham in, "A Royal Rival." A Play, in Four Acts, adapted by Gerald Du Maurier. With Prince Lloyd, Edwin Stevens, Snitz Edwards, N. L. Jelenko et al.
  - If I Were King, December 16, 1901 (Box 2)
    E. H. Sothern in "If I Were King," a play, by Justin Huntly McCarthy. Also with George W. Wilson, Arthur R. Lawrence, John Findlay, Norman Conniers, Henry J. Carvill et al.
  - The Second in Command, December 23, 1901 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents John Drew in "The Second in Command" by Robert Marshall. Also with Guy Standing, Oswald Yorke, Lionel Barrymore, Reginald Carrington et al.
  - The Liberty Belles, December 30, 1901 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger's Troubadours in "The Liberty Belles." A Musical Comedy, in Three Acts, by Harry B. Smith. With Etta Butler, Sandol Milliken, Augusta Glose, Edna Hunter, Lotta Faust et al. Stage Direction, Herbert Gresham.
  - The Messenger Boy, January 20, 1902 (Box 2)
    Nixon & Zimmerman present George Edwardes' London Gaiety Theatre success, "The Messenger Boy." Musical Comedy by James T. Tanner and Alfred Murray. Lyrics by Adrian Ross and Percy Greenbank. With James T. Powers, George Honey et al.
  - Mariana, February 3, 1902 (Box 2)
    First American Tour of Mrs. Patrick Campbell in "Mariana." A Play, in Four Acts, by Jose Echegaray. Adapted by James Monteith Graham. With Lucie Milner, Adeline Bourne, Herbert Waring, Daniel McCarthy et al.
  - Beyond Human Power, February 3, 1902 (Box 2)
    First American Tour of Mrs. Patrick Campbell in "Beyond Human Power." A Drama, in Two Acts, by Bjornstjerne Bjornson. Translated from the Norwegian by Miss Jessie Muir. Also with G. S. Titheradge, Charles E. Bryant, A. Bromley Davenport et al.
  - Alice of Old Vincennes, March 10, 1902 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Virginia Harned in Edward E. Rose's dramatization of Maurice Thompson's novel, "Alice of Old Vincennes." Also with, Margaret Gordon, Sadie Lauer, Helen Tracy et al.
  - Maid Marian, April 7, 1902 (Box 2)
    Engagement of The Bostonians in the Comic Opera, in Three Acts, "Maid Marian," a sequel to "Robin Hood." Book by Harry B. Smith; Music by Reginald DeKoven. With Henry Clay Barnabee, W. H. MacDonald, Frank Rushworth, Grace Van Studdiford et al.
  - The Way of the World, April 28, 1902 (Box 2)
    Elsie de Wolfe and Her Company, including John Mason and Sarah Cowell Le Moyne, in "The Way of the World" by Clyde Fitch. Also with Arnold Daly, Alison Skipworth, Harrison Hunter et al.
  - Francesca da Rimini [2 copies], May 5, 1902 (Box 2)
    Otis Skinner and Company in "Francesca da Rimini" by George H. Boker. With Mark Fenton, Mr. Skinner, Aubrey Boucicault, William Norris, E. A. Eberle et al.
  - Under Two Flags, May 12, 1902 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents, by arrangement with David Belasco, "Under Two Flags" by Paul M. Potter. A Drama, in Five Acts and Nine Tableaux. With Blanche Bates, Eugene Ormonde, Burr McIntosh et al.
  - Notre Dame, September 22, 1902 (Box 2)
    Daniel Frohman presents, a Dramatization of Victor Hugo's, "Notre Dame." Written for the stage, in Five Acts and Seven Tableaux, by Paul M. Potter. With Bertha Galland, Wallace Worsley, Frank Losee, George W. Barbler et al.
  - A Modern Magdalen, October 20, 1902 (Box 2)
    Amelia Bingham presents her Company in "A Modern Magdalen." A Four Act Play adapted by Hadden Chambers. With Henry E. Dixey, Mrs. Madge Carr Cooke, Lucille Spinney et al.
  - The Girl and the Judge, October 27, 1902 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents, Annie Russell in a new and original comedy in Four Acts, "The Girl and the Judge," by Clyde Fitch. Also with, Orrin Johnson, John Glendinning, Randolph Mordecai, Herbert Marion et al.
  - Du Barry, December 8, 1902 (Box 2)
    David Belasco presents Mrs. Leslie Carter, in his new play, "Du Barry." Also with C. A. Stevenson, Campbell Gollan, Beresford Webb, Henry Weaver, Sr., Hamilton Revelle, H. R. Roberts et al.
  - The Joy of Living, December 29, 1902 (Box 2)
    Mrs. Patrick Campbell and Her London Company in "The Joy of Living." In Five Acts, by Hermann Snudermann. Translated by Mrs. Wharton. Also with Frederick Kerr, Amy Lamborn, Vaughan Glaser et al. Direction of Charles Frohman.
  - The Stubbornness of Geraldine, January 5, 1903 (Box 2)
    Mary Mannering, under the management of Frank McKee, in "The Stubbornness of Geraldine." A Play, in Four Acts, by Clyde Fitch. Also with Amy Ricard, Mrs. Hone, Anita Rothe, Rosa Cooke, Marian Gardiner et al.
  - The Middleman [2 copies], January 19, 1903 (Box 2)
    Mr. E. S. Willard in "The Middleman" by Henry Arthur Jones. Also with Bassett Roe, A. S, Homewood, H. Cane, Ernest Stallard et al.
  - A Country Mouse, February 9, 1903 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Ethel Barrymore in a Comedy, in Three Acts, entitled "A Country Mouse." By Arthur Law. Also with Harry Davenport, George W. Howard, Bruce McRae et al.
  - The Cavalier, February 16, 1903 (Box 2)
    Julia Marlowe in "The Cavalier" by George W. Cable. Dramatized by Paul Kester and George Middleton. Charles B. Dillingham, Manager. Also with, Francis Kingdon, Clarence Handysides, Frank Worthing et al.
  - Iris, March 2, 1903 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Virginia Harned in "Iris." A Drama, in Five Acts, by A. W. Pinero. Also with Ethel Winthrop, Louise Drew, Elizabeth Goodall, Rachel Crown, Mabel Snider et al.
  - Soldiers of Fortune, March 16, 1903 (Box 2)
    Robert Edeson in, "Soldiers of Fortune," by Richard Harding Davis. Stage version by Augustus Thomas. Management, Henry B. Harris. Also with Gabriel Ravenelle, H. David Todd, Thomas Lawrence, Edwin Brandt et al.
  - King Dodo, March 23, 1903 (Box 2)
    Henry W. Savage presents "King Dodo," the Comedy Opera. Book by Frank Pixley; Music by Gustav Luders; Stage direction by Charles H. Jones. With Raymond Hitchcock, Ivar Anderson, Arthur Wooley et al.
  - Comedy of Errors, April 6, 1903 (Box 2)
    Stuart Robson, under the direction of Daniel V. Arthur, in "Comedy of Errors." By William Shakespeare. Also with Walker M. Dennett, Cecil Kingstone, Edward Mawsor et al.
  - The Eternal City, April 13, 1903 (Box 2)
    Viola Allen in "The Eternal City" by Hall Caine. Music composed and arranged by Pietro Mascagni. Stage Direction, E. W. Presbrey. Also with Edward Morgan, Frederic de Belleville et al.
  - Mademoiselle Mars, May 4, 1903 (Box 2)
    Mrs. Langtry and Her Company in, "Mademoiselle Mars," by Paul Kester. With William Humphrey, Matheson Lang, Felix Edwardes, Clayton Legge, Everard Digby et al.
  - Mr. Pickwick, May 11, 1903 (Box 2)
    De Wolf Hopper and Company, in a Musical based on Dickens' Masterpiece, "Mr. Pickwick." Music by Manuel Klein; Book by Charles Klein; Lyrics by Grant Stewart. With De Wolf Hopper, Digby Bell, Henry Norman et al.
  - Pretty Peggy, September 21, 1903 (Box 2)
    Grace George in "Pretty Peggy" by Frances Aymar Mathews. Also with James M. Bowman, Adolph Bernard, Donald MacLaren, Kingsley Benedict et al.
  - The Rogers Brothers in London, November 9, 1903 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger present The Rogers Brothers (Gus and Max) in John J. McNally's latest, "The Rogers Brothers in London." Music by Max Hoffman and Melville Ellis; Lyrics by George V. Hobart and Ed. Gardenier; Staged by Herbert Gresham and Ned Wayburn.
  - Sergeant Kitty, November 16, 1903 (Box 2)
    Mr. George R. White presents The Virginia Earl Opera Company in "Sergeant Kitty." Book and lyrics by R. H. Burnside. Music by A. Baldwin Sloane. With Sylvain Langlois, Harry Stone, Albert Parr, Junie McCree, Chas. Renwick, Harry Braham et al.
  - Captain Dieppe, November 23, 1903 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents John Drew in, "Captain Dieppe," by Anthony Hope and Harrison Rhodes. Also with George Howard, Charles Lane, Louis Baker, Sydney Herbert et al.
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, December 7, 1903 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger present N. C. Goodwin in Shakespeare's "A Midsummer Night's Dream." Music of Mendelssohn arranged by Victor Herbert. Stage Direction of Herbert Gresham and E. D. Lyons. Also with Margaret Crawford, Thelma Fair et al.
  - The Runaways, December 14, 1903 (Box 2)
    Sam S. Shubert and Nixon & Zimmerman present Fay Templeton in the musical "The Runaways." Direction of Sam S. Shubert. Book by Addison Burkhardt. Score by Raymond Hubbell. Also with Alexander Clark, Van Rensselaer Wheeler et al.
  - The Merchant of Venice, December 21, 1903 (Box 2)